<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.6.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-06-25T15:47:01+10:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title type="html">Stratapp Website</title><subtitle>Stratapp Site for Forestry.io</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Accelerating x-Border Performance</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019-06-25-accelerating-x-border-performance/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Accelerating x-Border Performance" /><published>2019-06-25T15:30:25+10:00</published><updated>2019-06-25T15:30:25+10:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/accelerating-x-border-performance</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019-06-25-accelerating-x-border-performance/">&lt;p&gt;With so much hype on technology innovation - e.g. robotics and artificial intelligence - it is easy to overlook the massive ground shift taking place on org design. Teams are fast becoming a mix of onshore and offshore resources, that work together as if they were sitting under the same roof.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Historically offshoring was only accessible to large corporates, undertaken predominantly as outsourcing discrete functions and processes. Hence the rise of call centers and large IT support teams in India since the 1980s, with somewhat variable outcomes for end customers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Technological change and affordability (voice, video and collaboration apps) have since made offshoring globally accessible to small and mid-market companies. In the early to mid 2000’s, their approach followed the same path of corporates, asking:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“What projects or discrete functions can be offshored?”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then from around 2010 onwards, the thinking of SMBs and mid-market companies evolved to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“How do I extend my onshore teams to be a mix of onshore and offshore?”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This shift has rapidly fuelled the emerging seat and staff leasing sector, with most service providers growing at 25-40% per annum in the Philippines since 2014.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Australian politicians, tier-1 consultants and senior executives in corporates seem oblivious to this massive change taking place in the two market segments that employ the most people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whilst the timeline of Scott Linden-Jones’ predictions in his excellent book, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/The-Third-Wave-Micro-globalism-employment/dp/1482088231&quot;&gt;The Third Wave&lt;/a&gt;, were slightly ambitious, we believe his thinking is sound and this third wave of industrial change will have an irreversible impact on Australia. The book offers several positives on what can be done and some lateral thinking on the future career options for y-generation and those younger - anyone who has children should study these carefully.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you embrace the trend of x-border teams that work together seamlessly as if they were one team onshore - as opposed to only offshoring low-skilled work, projects or discrete functions - then you will see how #stratapp empowers x-border strategic alignment and effective day to day execution across different time zones, geographies and cultures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At #stratapp, we’re walking the same talk. #stratapp is designed, built, supported and run by teams that are a healthy mix of onshore and offshore resources, working together as one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Australians love to innovate and solve problems, rather than get bogged down in repetitive tasks or process detail, so at #stratapp we make these attributes the focus of our onshore resources.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Source: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/The-Third-Wave-Micro-globalism-employment/dp/1482088231&quot; title=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/The-Third-Wave-Micro-globalism-employment/dp/1482088231&quot;&gt;https://www.amazon.com/The-Third-Wave-Micro-globalism-employment/dp/1482088231&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Ash Richardson</name></author><summary type="html">With so much hype on technology innovation - e.g. robotics and artificial intelligence - it is easy to overlook the massive ground shift taking place on org design. Teams are fast becoming a mix of onshore and offshore resources, that work together as if they were sitting under the same roof.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Millennials in the Workplace</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019-06-25-millennials-in-the-workplace/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Millennials in the Workplace" /><published>2019-06-25T15:28:22+10:00</published><updated>2019-06-25T15:28:22+10:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/millennials-in-the-workplace</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019-06-25-millennials-in-the-workplace/">&lt;p&gt;At the link below is an excellent interview with Simon Sinek on Inside Quest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In our view, the next generation workforce are just magic, a breath of fresh air. They are all about collaboration and interaction. They don’t mind sharing real time drafts of work in progress. They hate pretending to work and they don’t go looking for work that doesn’t make sense. Contrary to us older folks, they actually love transparency and accountability. They just want it to be real. Not vague goals or ambiguous roles. They want clarity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;#stratapp gives them clarity, like never before. #stratapp makes it easy for them to contribute to the work of others and to see exactly where they fit in with what the organization is trying to achieve.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sure, part of y-gen’s motivation is to learn and progress, but there is a deeper, more complex driver to why millennials think and act this way. #stratapp frees them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How many executives and senior managers do you hear say they were up at 5am this morning, or late Sunday night, catching up on email. Y-generation detest this behaviour and the culture it promotes. For them, replying to 100 emails per day is not work - it is a waste of time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For y-generation: email = reset password,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;… so you can get back into the application you want to use&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;#stratapp kills internal email. #stratapp helps switch the whole organization to social collaboration, however #stratapp is the first application to do this with both context and structure. That is, the social conversations in #stratapp take place within the relevant context of strategy and day to day work. Not only that, the social posts have structure, making it easy for anyone at any level to quickly filter conversations by attributes such as decisions, questions, approvals, ideas and risks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;#stratapp uniquely meets the expectations of both current and next generation workers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Source: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hER0Qp6QJNU&quot; title=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hER0Qp6QJNU&quot;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hER0Qp6QJNU&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Ash Richardson</name></author><summary type="html">At the link below is an excellent interview with Simon Sinek on Inside Quest.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">How great leaders inspire action</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019-06-25-how-great-leaders-inspire-action/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How great leaders inspire action" /><published>2019-06-25T15:27:40+10:00</published><updated>2019-06-25T15:27:40+10:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/how-great-leaders-inspire-action</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019-06-25-how-great-leaders-inspire-action/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“People don’t buy what you do, they buy why you do it. And what you do simply proves what you believe.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Simon Sinek has become a global phenomenon since this TED talk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He particularly resonates with y-generation. #stratapp is deliberately designed for the current and next generation workforce - both audiences want to know why their organization exists.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;#stratapp’s strategy module includes a Why page - it is optional, but we’d love you to turn it on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Source: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ted.com/talks/simon_sinek_how_great_leaders_inspire_action&quot; title=&quot;https://www.ted.com/talks/simon_sinek_how_great_leaders_inspire_action&quot;&gt;https://www.ted.com/talks/simon_sinek_how_great_leaders_inspire_action&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Simon Sinek</name></author><summary type="html">“People don’t buy what you do, they buy why you do it. And what you do simply proves what you believe.”</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Employee engagement without business performance is a fail. Business performance without employee engagement is a fail.</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019-06-25-employee-engagement-without-business-performance-is-a-fail-business-performance-without-employee-engagement-is-a-fail/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Employee engagement without business performance is a fail.  Business performance without employee engagement is a fail." /><published>2019-06-25T15:25:12+10:00</published><updated>2019-06-25T15:25:12+10:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/employee-engagement-without-business-performance-is-a-fail-business-performance-without-employee-engagement-is-a-fail</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019-06-25-employee-engagement-without-business-performance-is-a-fail-business-performance-without-employee-engagement-is-a-fail/">&lt;p&gt;Anthony Moorhouse is the founder of &lt;a href=&quot;http://coherentstrat.com/&quot;&gt;Coherent Strategy&lt;/a&gt;, the first boutique advisory firm established to coach and support #stratapp clients on implementation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Coherent Strategy apply the Gallup Q12 Index to measure employee engagement over time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Gallup Q12 Index is derived from 30 years of in-depth behavioral and economic research involving 17 million employees. Gallup has identified 12 core questions - the Q12 - that have emerged to best predict employee and business performance:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you know what is expected of you at work?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Do you have the materials and equipment to do your work right?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;At work, do you have the opportunity to do what you do best every day?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;In the last seven days, have you received recognition or praise for doing good work?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Does your supervisor, or someone at work, seem to care about you as a person?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Is there someone at work who encourages your development?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;At work, do your opinions seem to count?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Does the mission/purpose of your company make you feel your job is important?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Are your associates (fellow employees) committed to doing quality work?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Do you have a best friend at work?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;In the last six months, has someone at work talked to you about your progress?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;In the last year, have you had opportunities to learn and grow?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Source: &lt;a href=&quot;https://q12.gallup.com/public/en-us/Features&quot; title=&quot;https://q12.gallup.com/public/en-us/Features&quot;&gt;https://q12.gallup.com/public/en-us/Features&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Anthony Moorhouse</name></author><summary type="html">Anthony Moorhouse is the founder of Coherent Strategy, the first boutique advisory firm established to coach and support #stratapp clients on implementation.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">#stratapp is easy to implement, but clients still manage change for the best results</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019-06-25-stratapp-is-easy-to-implement-but-clients-still-manage-change-for-the-best-results/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="#stratapp is easy to implement, but clients still manage change for the best results" /><published>2019-06-25T15:23:45+10:00</published><updated>2019-06-25T15:23:45+10:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/stratapp-is-easy-to-implement-but-clients-still-manage-change-for-the-best-results</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019-06-25-stratapp-is-easy-to-implement-but-clients-still-manage-change-for-the-best-results/">&lt;p&gt;SaaS product companies typically lock their clients into a prepaid contract, then leave the client to figure out the implementation by themselves, or with ‘&lt;em&gt;preferred partners&lt;/em&gt;’.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Their approach is usually hands-off and justified as building a scalable operating model. That is, most SaaS companies see their core business as scaling lead generation, onboarding and viral growth, alongside ongoing development.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This creates a problem for the client: implementation. CRM applications are a great example. Clients get excited at what’s possible during the sales process, then find themselves with a complex product that needs to be configured from a blank shell, and having to select from a range of preferred partners offering different advice, methodologies, resources and pricing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In contrast, #stratapp is configured to work ‘&lt;em&gt;out of the box&lt;/em&gt;’, so our preferred partners and the client can focus their energy and resources on proactively managing change and getting their teams fully engaged on what’s possible and understanding how #stratapp will benefit them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On partners, we have decided not to be hands-off. We need partners in order to scale geographically, this is unavoidable. But we are doing it differently. We have developed an implementation methodology for our partners and we have worked out what the implementation coaching costs should be for our clients, at each step in that methodology.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This approach breaks new ground for SaaS. There are three reasons we are doing this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;We are walking the talk on genuinely caring about our clients’ success, and to do that we need to directly influence how they are supported by our partners&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;It removes the pressure on clients, and partners, to negotiate on implementation pricing&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;It ensures a value for money outcome, for every client&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We will also be breaking new ground on communities - how we bring together and collaborate across clients, partners and interested users. We will share more on that later this year.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Ash Richardson </name></author><summary type="html">SaaS product companies typically lock their clients into a prepaid contract, then leave the client to figure out the implementation by themselves, or with ‘preferred partners’.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">How to run a company with (almost) no rules</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019-06-25-how-to-run-a-company-with-almost-no-rules/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How to run a company with (almost) no rules" /><published>2019-06-25T15:21:50+10:00</published><updated>2019-06-25T15:21:50+10:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/how-to-run-a-company-with-almost-no-rules</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019-06-25-how-to-run-a-company-with-almost-no-rules/">&lt;p&gt;Ricardo Semler shot to fame with his book Maverick, which cut to the core of empowering employees, whilst pragmatically addressing human constraints and positive attributes in a fresh way, when undertaking org design.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;#stratapp’s real-time transparency and collaboration, across the whole organization, provides an easy and compelling way to engage talent at all levels like never before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you decide to combine #stratapp’s world first capability in strategy+execution+collaboration with the progressive lateral thinking of Ricardo Semler, we would love to hear from you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Source:&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ted.com/talks/ricardo_semler_how_to_run_a_company_with_almost_no_rules?language=en&quot; title=&quot;https://www.ted.com/talks/ricardo_semler_how_to_run_a_company_with_almost_no_rules?language=en&quot;&gt; https://www.ted.com/talks/ricardo_semler_how_to_run_a_company_with_almost_no_rules?language=en&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Ricardo Semler</name></author><summary type="html">Ricardo Semler shot to fame with his book Maverick, which cut to the core of empowering employees, whilst pragmatically addressing human constraints and positive attributes in a fresh way, when undertaking org design.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Measure what matters</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019-06-25-measure-what-matters/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Measure what matters" /><published>2019-06-25T15:18:37+10:00</published><updated>2019-06-25T15:18:37+10:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/measure-what-matters</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019-06-25-measure-what-matters/">&lt;p&gt;John Doerr’s book and life’s work have given all of us access to the clear thinking and progressive management practices of Intel’s Andy Grove, who was decades ahead of his time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Google has applied the OKR methodology every quarter since 1999, evolving it to two types of OKRs - committed and aspirational. Google expects 100% results on Committed OKRs and about 70% on Aspirational OKRs, the latter deliberately stretching the capabilities of individuals and the organization.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To achieve aspirational performance, John convincingly argues the case for decoupling salary and bonuses from OKRs, elegantly explained here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.whatmatters.com/resources/compensation-salary-bonuses-without-okrs&quot;&gt;Compensation The Right Way: Without OKRs.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Leaders must get across the why as well as the what. Their people need more than milestones for motivation. They are thirsting for meaning, to understand how their goals relate to the mission.“&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“There are so many people working so hard and achieving so little.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Ideas are easy. Execution is everything.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“When people have conflicting priorities or unclear, meaningless, or arbitrarily shifting goals, they become frustrated, cynical, and demotivated.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With #stratapp, leaders deliver org-wide clarity on the why, direction and goals, coupled with real-time collaboration and transparency on execution. This helps the CEO to bring everyone at all levels in the organization along the same journey.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;OKRs can be cascaded and tracked through a hierarchy of workboards inside #stratapp, with contextual links to the corresponding strategic goals &amp;gt; objectives &amp;gt; actions &amp;gt; projects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In future we will be adding more features on setting, categorizing, cascading, tracking and reviewing quarterly and annual OKRs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Source: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.whatmatters.com&quot; title=&quot;https://www.whatmatters.com&quot;&gt;https://www.whatmatters.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>John Doerr</name></author><summary type="html">John Doerr’s book and life’s work have given all of us access to the clear thinking and progressive management practices of Intel’s Andy Grove, who was decades ahead of his time.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Many strategies fail because they’re not actually strategies</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019-06-25-many-strategies-fail-because-they-re-not-actually-strategies/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Many strategies fail because they’re not actually strategies" /><published>2019-06-25T15:16:06+10:00</published><updated>2019-06-25T15:16:06+10:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/many-strategies-fail-because-they-re-not-actually-strategies</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019-06-25-many-strategies-fail-because-they-re-not-actually-strategies/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“The strategy consultants come in, do their work, and document the new strategy in a PowerPoint presentation and a weighty report. Town hall meetings are organized, employees are told to change their behavior, balanced scorecards are reformulated, and budgets are set aside to support initiatives that fit the new strategy. And then nothing happens.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s been the way for the last 30 years. Static strategy documents that tend to be communicated top-down and tied to stretch, reasonable or conservative measures/KPIs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We see there are two problems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first, articulated by Freek Vermeulen as: &lt;em&gt;“A real strategy involves a clear set of choices that define what the firm is going to do and what it’s not going to do.”&lt;/em&gt; This point is convincingly argued by Richard Rumelt, mentioned &lt;strong&gt;in our other article.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The second, is the need to break the age old paradigm of static documents and the terrible human experience of communicating via email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;#stratapp helps solve both problems, not only by killing internal email. When you start to articulate your strategy inside #stratapp, the transparency and tree hierarchy naturally drives clarity in strategic choices. There are no static documents and all social collaboration takes place within the context of that hierarchy - so instead of just adding more noise, the social engagement, at all levels of the organization, has a direct and meaningful impact on strategic choices, strategy development, execution planning, execution and the evolution of those four.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Source: &lt;a href=&quot;https://hbr.org/2017/11/many-strategies-fail-because-theyre-not-actually-strategies&quot; title=&quot;https://hbr.org/2017/11/many-strategies-fail-because-theyre-not-actually-strategies&quot;&gt;https://hbr.org/2017/11/many-strategies-fail-because-theyre-not-actually-strategies&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Freek Vermeulen</name></author><summary type="html">“The strategy consultants come in, do their work, and document the new strategy in a PowerPoint presentation and a weighty report. Town hall meetings are organized, employees are told to change their behavior, balanced scorecards are reformulated, and budgets are set aside to support initiatives that fit the new strategy. And then nothing happens.”</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Your strategy should be a hypothesis you constantly adjust</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2018-02-15-articleyeah/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Your strategy should be a hypothesis you constantly adjust" /><published>2018-02-15T19:09:13+10:00</published><updated>2018-02-15T19:09:13+10:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/articleyeah</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2018-02-15-articleyeah/">&lt;p&gt;This article on evolving strategy as you learn, goes to the heart of #stratapp.  We wholeheartedly agree and go further to say that strategy should be given a heartbeat, freed from static documents that are out of date within weeks and soon forgotten by the next quarter.  Enter #stratapp, where your strategy and execution can be transparently evolved in real time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“What is new is the idea that closing the gap between strategy and execution may not be about better execution after all, but rather about better learning — about more dialogue between strategy and operations, a greater flow of information from customers to executives, and more experiments. In today’s fast-paced world, strategy as learning must go hand in hand with execution as learning — bypassing the idea that either a strategy or the execution is flawed — to recognize that both are necessarily flawed and both are valuable sources of learning, improvement, and reinvention.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Source: https://hbr.org/2017/11/your-strategy-should-be-a-hypothesis-you-constantly-adjust&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Amy Edmondson and Paul Verdin</name></author><category term="Demo" /><category term="Forestry" /><summary type="html">This article on evolving strategy as you learn, goes to the heart of #stratapp. We wholeheartedly agree and go further to say that strategy should be given a heartbeat, freed from static documents that are out of date within weeks and soon forgotten by the next quarter. Enter #stratapp, where your strategy and execution can be transparently evolved in real time.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">How to excel at both strategy and execution</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2017-02-12-modern/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How to excel at both strategy and execution" /><published>2017-09-25T19:09:13+10:00</published><updated>2017-09-25T19:09:13+10:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/modern</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2017-02-12-modern/">&lt;p&gt;“According to a global survey of 700 executives across a variety of industries, conducted by the strategy consulting division of PwC, only 8% of company leaders were said to excel at both strategy and execution.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“…a bold vision needs to include both a very ambitious destination and a well-conceived path for execution that will get you there.“&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Leaders who master both strategy and execution start by building a bold but executable strategy. Next, they ensure that the company is investing behind the change. And last, they make sure the entire organization is motivated to go the journey.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is exactly why #stratapp is not a strategy-only application.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;#stratapp enables all leaders, regardless of their underlying skill orientation, to deliver on both strategy and execution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Source: https://hbr.org/2017/11/how-to-excel-at-both-strategy-and-execution&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Paul Leinwand and Joachim Rotering</name></author><summary type="html">“According to a global survey of 700 executives across a variety of industries, conducted by the strategy consulting division of PwC, only 8% of company leaders were said to excel at both strategy and execution.”</summary></entry></feed>